So I have a question for y'all. A lot of times I see folks say, well, we can't do such and such
unless we get organized. What does organized look like to y'all? And I'll bring you up on camera.
What does organized look like to y'all? Door knocking in town halls. I think a lot of y'all's
version of organized is a bit fantastical because I think a lot of people's idea of organized
is like everybody, like meetings and pamphlets. And I think your version of organized is
based on maybe what you have seen from like the 60s, not realizing that we live in a different
timeframe. And so organized is going to be realized differently. And I think that we
also have, we live particularly in the United States in a management mindset. Everybody wants
to be managed. Y'all got managers. You want to be told what to do. You want to be told how
to do it. And there's a failure to understand the individual responsibility that is required
of you, regardless of leadership coming from somewhere else. There's something to be said
for organized, meaning simply just being on the same page. Now the real organizing, in my opinion,
comes from, comes into what are the things that are in place after. That's the organizing.
However, so many of us are caught up in this mindset of, I can't because. And I talk about
the failure of imagination in this book, by the way, Gio, but that's really like a big handicap.
I can't because. I can't because. And I see so many of the, I can't because being grounded in,
we got to be organized. I don't want to be the first to do it. I don't want to do it by myself.
You know, when I see people have this expectation that it's going to like come online, like in a
digital space, like we're going to organize in the same way that like folks said, everyone put up
black squares. It says to me, Oh, that's how y'all think it's going to go down. And I'm here,
I'm here to tell you, I, I disagree. Now there are organizations and factions that 100% organize
around direct action. Facts. However, there's a larger reality that really is.
Um, what are you about? Someone asked, do I believe that not everyone was built to lead or
have those qualities? I don't think built is the word. I think people are hampered by trauma and fear.
And that could be in their own experiences or DNA that they carry down, which is what you mean by
built to. However, I do, I, I will always believe that there is going to have to be concerted effort
at shift. And I just, I just refuse, I just refuse to
not continue to push that as a demand. I just refuse. And, um, you know, if that's considered idealistic,
then so be it. But, you know, I'm going to always push that. And the failure to make that shift
is going, it is what it is. It, but it also just puts you in a different place. You know,
there are people that I remove from my Instagram once I see, you know, what they're on. And it's
like, oh, you don't get to stay here anymore. You don't get to be in community with us. And I can
see that Instagram is shadow banning me right now. What can those of us with small children do to fight
back and be radical? Raise radicals. You can start there. I think it really becomes a matter of what
everybody is, um, doing within their immediate communities and what everybody is actually
asking of themselves. But I'm going to tell you now, there is no version of that. There's no version
of this that comes without struggle. There is no version. And people wear struggle differently.
You know what I'm saying? Like people will look at me and be like, oh, you're so privileged. I'm like,
you don't even know my struggle. I'll be good, Zavon Trey. Fill out the form on my website, baby.
The book will never be available on Amazon because I am not selling my book on Amazon. My book is only
available on AmandaSeals.com and AmandaLandExports.com. That's it. When we talk about
what is organized, I just want to, in a time of new, we are in a time of different. We are in a time
that is not mirrored exactly by any other time. So there's going to be versions of how we challenge
that have never been done before. This is innovation. So, you know, when, when you ask,
like, so you, you can't just be looking at the past and saying, if it doesn't look like that,
it ain't it. You have to be asking yourself, what is that version of that look like for now?
So, you know, and that's why I always press about having, um, I always press about having
imagination. No, I, again, tomorrow is thanks taking. And I saw so many people being like, well,
yeah, but I still got it. I bought food for lunch and dinner tomorrow. And that's what I'm going to eat.
And, um, and I also think people think that there has to be like some majority. I don't know. I
think, I think y'all really want there to be the people that you see in like the biggest spaces doing
the thing and they're never going to do it. The people you see with the biggest platforms are usually
the most cowardly. They're the most cowardly because in their mind, they have the most to lose
when in actuality, they already possess the most. So even if they have the most to lose,
they have the easier route to reset. So when people are like, Oh, you know, Amanda,
you're coming from a place of privilege. I'm just coming from a place of, I know I'm going to be
all right. Just cause I'm always going to be all right. Like that's just where I am in this,
in this life. I'm just always going to be all right. I don't know what I did in the previous life,
but I have learned that I'm always going to be all right in this particular life.
Like that's just it. And y'all, you may want to see me struggle, et cetera. I'm, I'm always going
to be all right. My ancestors for some, for some reason, my ancestors are like, not her.
They do not play about me. They don't play about me. And, and just so you know, let's say I got
assassinated tomorrow. I was still all right. Okay. I stopped asking questions about it because
it's just what it is. So I'm just out here just living my best and knowing that I'm going to be
all right doing the most. Oh, Joe, but I just, the frame is too small. Um, my vision of the future
on a very basic level, my vision of the future is a people aware of how much we have in terms of
this planet and each other and thus united in protecting that. A vision of the future is
thank you, Carrie L. Jones. I really am. A vision of the future is an educated proletariat.
Uh, you know, we once had like entire civilizations. I hear minds like you BJG and Deshaun Harris,
but excommunication is used to make you all Cassandra not being heard. How do you feel about
reach or conversations when media literacy has been lowered? Um, I mean, it is what it is.
Some days I'm, some days I'm annoyed by it. Some days I'm not. Hey, hey, hey. Jordi, come over here.
Don't, don't go bother her. Now y'all be wondering what is the sound that's, that that's being made on
Amanda's couch when she's talking. Those are tarps. I live in a house now where I got to put a tarp over
the goddamn couch every time I get up. It's been happening so long that I've, I've created a
mechanism. You know how long something got to be going on to have a mechanism? Jesus. But I caught
her just now. Caught her in the act. She's about to do it. She's about to get down, down. And I caught
her, I caught her in the act, but she's not going to let me give her the gabapentin right now. That's
what I really need to do is give her the gabapentin. I'm trying to figure out behaviorally when she does
it. When does she be peeing on this damn couch? What is it that's happening to her in her mind?
What is it that's driving her to say, you know what? Fuck that little box. I'm gonna go pee on
that damn couch. And I can't figure it out. I genuinely can't figure it out. Hooray!
Everybody else came but her. If you all, it was, it was a Pied Piper moment just now. Everybody else
came around the corner except for the cat that I was calling. And now Instagram is doing the thing
where it stops showing me my comments because it's a hater. Jordi, that's not for you. Anyways,
well, now I can't see the comments. So it's over. Good night, everybody.